(Sheldon:)Well, to celebrate
this reconciliation,
(Sheldon:)let's all share a milk shake.
(Sheldon:)Penny, you'll need a straw.
(Jesse:)-You're back.
-Yes, I am!
(Bernadette:)There's a few more things
I want to say to you.
(Bernadette:)Stuart's store is just fine, and he's
a much nicer person than you are,
and it you still have that comic,
I'd like to buy it right now!
(Jesse:)No problem.
(Jesse:)Oh, you want a latte
while you wait?
No, I don't want a latte!
(Bernadette:)I want a cappuccino
and a blueberry scene!
(Jesse:)-I only have chocolate chip.
-Well, that sounds even better!
(Bert:)Thanks for coming to the
mineral and rock show with me.
(Raj:)We're sorry Amy didn't want to go.
(Howard:)Really, really sorry.
Nah, who needs her
when I have you guys?
(Bert:)Rock show!
Rock show! Rock show!
(Bert:)Rock show! Rock show!
(Bert:)Rock show!
Rock show!